{"componentChunkName":"component---src-templates-establishment-page-js","path":"/establishment/1628","result":{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"1628","name":"Hannan Center","address":"4750 Woodward Ave.","zipcode":"48201","owner":"Hannan Center","licenseNumber":"078720","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Temporarily Closed","riskCategory":"Medium","reviewFrequencyDays":"335","coords":"-83.06306,42.35568","geojson":{"id":"1628","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.063063503,42.35567799]},"properties":{"name":"Hannan Center","owner":"Hannan Center","address":"4750 Woodward Ave.","zipcode":"48201","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":"Medium","license_number":"078720","establishmentid":"1628","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Temporarily Closed","review_frequency_days":"335","most_recent_license_date":"26/4/2022"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"4807","name":"Commonwealth Street Catering, LLC","address":"4750 Woodward Ave.","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"4861","name":"Ms. Ruth Catering","address":"4750 Woodward Ave.","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"5086","name":"Operation ABLE of Michigan- Det Training","address":"4750 Woodward Ave.","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"4860","name":"Detroit Gypsy Kitchen","address":"4750 Woodward","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"2444","name":"Association of Chinese Americans","address":"4750 Woodward Ave.","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"51622624","name":"Operation ABLE of Michigan Site #2","address":"33 E. Forest","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"1879","name":"First Congregational Church","address":"33 Forest Ave. E.","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"1718","name":"Cathedral Church of St. Paul","address":"4800 Woodward Ave.","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"5158","name":"Red Pepper Foods","address":"4800 Woodward Ave.","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"1905","name":"Robinson Dairy Vending","address":"4747 Woodward","zipcode":"48201"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"60822","inspectionDate":"2022-11-21T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-501.14","violationDescription":"A WAREWASHING machine; the compartments of sinks, basins, or  other receptacles used for washing and rinsing EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, or raw FOODS, or laundering wiping cloths; and drainboards or other EQUIPMENT used to substitute for drainboards shall be cleaned as required.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Warewashing equipment","subItem":"three compartment sink basins","problemDescription":"Not cleaned","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Three compartment sink","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean as required above."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Cooler (reach-in)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair"},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"NON FOOD CONTACT SURFACES","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"violationCode":"6-501.18","violationDescription":"PLUMBING FIXTURES such as HANDWASHING SINKS, toilets, and urinals shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean. \n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"sink","subItem":"handwash","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Handsink","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean"},{"violationCode":"4-602.12","violationDescription":"(A) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking and baking EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at least every 24 hours. This section does not apply to hot oil cooking and filtering EQUIPMENT if it is cleaned as specified in Subparagraph 4-602.11(D)(6).   \n(B) The cavities and door seals of microwave ovens shall be cleaned at least every 24 hours by using the manufacturer's recommended cleaning procedure.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Baking and cooking equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not cleaned","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Cooking equipment","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean as required above."}]},{"inspectionid":"58283","inspectionDate":"2022-03-31T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"57414","inspectionDate":"2022-02-23T00:00:00","inspectionType":"COVID19-temp closed","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"51464","inspectionDate":"2020-03-16T00:00:00","inspectionType":"COVID19-temp closed","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"49743","inspectionDate":"2019-10-29T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"44669","inspectionDate":"2018-11-06T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-501.112","violationDescription":"In a mechanical operation, the temperature of the fresh hot water SANITIZING rinse as it enters the manifold may not be more than 194 F, or less than 165 F for stationary rack machines or 180 F for all other machines to assure proper sanitizing of utensils. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Dish machine final rinse temperature","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Less than 180 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"DISH MACHINE","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair to provide temperature stated above."},{"violationCode":"5-103.11","violationDescription":"(A) The water source and system shall be of sufficient capacity to meet the peak water demands of the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT. (Pf)\n(B) Hot water generation and distribution systems shall be sufficient to meet the peak hot water demands throughout the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Hot water supply","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Insufficient to meet demands","subProblem":"","location":"THROUGHOUT FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide sufficient supply if hot water such as a larger or additional hot water heater."},{"violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Dishwasher area","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":""},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Sink (3-compartment/basins)","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":""}]},{"inspectionid":"38532","inspectionDate":"2017-04-19T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Grease trap","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2023-04-13T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"1628"}},"staticQueryHashes":["3649515864","63159454"]}